Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
: Help!
： 帮助！
Hey, yah!
嘿，呀！
Help, help.
救命，救命。
Whoa, stop.
哇，停下来。
There, there,
you're safe now, little lady.
那里，那里，
你现在安全了，小女士。
You fool.
你这个傻瓜。
You've fallen into my trap.
你已经掉进我的陷阱里了。
Now you're mine,
SpongeBob the strong.
现在你是我的了
海绵宝宝强者。
So we meet again, crazyfish.
所以我们又见面了，疯狂的鱼。
Bring it on.
来吧。
With pleasure.
荣幸。
: So loud.
: 这么大声。
You ready to get crazy,
huh, crazyfish?
你准备好疯狂了
哈，疯鱼？
You bet your frosting,
sponge-cake.
你打赌你的糖霜，
海绵蛋糕。
Sorry, I'm not wearing
any frosting.
抱歉，我没穿
任何糖霜。
Hey, that's cheating.
嘿，那是作弊。
No, it's not.
不，不是。
Yes, it is.
是的。
Is not.
不是。
Is not, is not...
不是、不是……
Um, guys?
嗯，伙计们？
Anyway, your shoe's untied.
不管怎样，你的鞋带已经解开了。
Is not!
不是！
Guys.
伙计们。
Is too, is too...
太、太……
The train!
火车！
Don't worry, I'm ready.
别担心，我已经准备好了。
Bring it on.
来吧。
Oh, good morning Gare-bear.
哦，早上好，小熊车站。
Meow.
喵。
I kept you up all night
with my nocturnal outbursts?
我让你彻夜难眠
我的夜间爆发？
Again?
再次？
Meow?
喵？
No, no, Tuesday night
was the one
不不不，周二晚上
就是那个
with the 30-foot librarian.
与30英尺高的图书管理员。
Last night was the one
where I defeat
昨晚就是那个
我打败的地方
notorious arch-villain
Jack M. Crazyfish
臭名昭著的大恶棍
杰克·M·疯狂鱼
using the sheer force
使用纯粹的力量
of my awesomely
developed musculature.
我的真棒
发达的肌肉组织。
Whew, what a relief.
哇，真是松了一口气。
For a second there I thought
I gave myself a black...
有那么一瞬间我想
我给了自己一个黑...
Whoa... Oh.
哇...哦。
Eye.
眼睛。
Meow.
喵。
Go away, Gary.
走开，加里。
I'm busy... Wallowing.
我很忙... 打滚。
Meow?
喵？
I did something
so dumb to myself
我做了一些事
对自己来说太愚蠢了
that even you would laugh
uncontrollably at me.
连你都会笑
无法控制地对着我。
: Meow.
: 喵。
You promise you won't laugh?
你保证不笑？
OK, here goes.
好的，开始了。
Gary, I gave myself
a black eye
加里，我给了自己
一只黑眼圈
trying to open
the toothpaste.
试图打开
牙膏。
Thanks for not laughing, Gare.
谢谢你没有笑，Gare。
I knew you'd...
我就知道你会...
Gare?
车站？
Hi, SpongeBob.
嗨，海绵宝宝。
Hey, cool glasses.
嘿，很酷的眼镜。
Can I try them on... Oh!
我可以试穿一下吗...哦！
SpongeBob, your eye.
海绵宝宝，你的眼睛。
It's all black and swollen.
浑身又黑又肿。
How'd you mess
your eye up, SpongeBob?
你怎么搞砸了
海绵宝宝，你的眼睛抬起来了吗？
Did somebody hit you?
有人打你吗？
Where is he?
他在哪儿？
Yeah, we'll settle
this like men.
是的，我们会解决的
这就像男人一样。
We'll sue him.
我们会起诉他。
No, no, it's OK, Patrick.
不，不，没关系，帕特里克。
He, uh...
他，呃…
He learned his lesson.
他吸取了教训。
Are you sure, SpongeBob?
你确定吗，海绵宝宝？
Who was this guy anyway?
这家伙到底是谁？
Hmm...
唔...
It was Jack M. Crazyfish.
这是杰克·M·疯狂鱼。
You've never seen anyone
like this guy, Patrick.
你从未见过任何人
就像帕特里克这个人。
He was about 60 feet tall.
他大约有 60 英尺高。
: Oh.
： 哦。
Yeah, he was big and mean.
是的，他又大又刻薄。
Oh, but ol' SpongeBob here
哦，但是海绵宝宝在这里
knows how to teach
a lummox some manners.
知道如何教学
一些礼仪上的笨拙。
What did you do?
你做了什么？
I handled him
the same way I handle
我对付他
和我处理的方式一样
all enormous
muscle-bound villains.
都巨大的
肌肉发达的恶棍。
With tears?
带着泪水？
Uh, no, with a little
呃，不，有一点
Hi-yah!
嗨呀！
And a ka-zow!
还有一声卡佐！
And a gallon of
hi-yah, hi-yah, ha!
还有一加仑
嗨呀，嗨呀，哈！
Yeah, he never
knew what hit 'em.
是的，他从来没有
知道是什么击中了他们。
Well, then what happened?
嗯，然后发生了什么？
I woke up...
Oh, I mean, I...
我醒了...
哦，我是说，我...
I know exactly what you mean.
我完全明白你的意思。
You whooped him
with your eyes closed.
你对他大喊大叫
闭上眼睛。
That is exactly
what I mean, Patrick.
那正是
我的意思是，帕特里克。
Well, see you later, buddy.
好吧，待会儿见，伙计。
There goes a real hero.
真正的英雄走了。
Wha, wah-bah-bah!
哇、哇、哇、哇！
Slugger,
that's me.
重击手，
那是我。
What the?
什么？
Yee haw.
哎哟。
Get along little fishies.
和小鱼儿相处吧。
Hi, Sandy.
嗨，桑迪。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Hot catsnake in a barn.
谷仓里的热猫蛇。
Look at your eye.
看看你的眼睛。
Land sakes.
土地缘故。
That's quite a shiner
you got there.
这是相当耀眼的
你到了那里。
Well, don't you worry none.
好吧，你不用担心。
I know some natural
remedies that'll...
我知道一些自然的
补救措施将...
Keep your natural
remedies to yourself.
保持你的自然
对自己的补救措施。
Manly dudes like
me don't need 'em.
有男子气概的男人喜欢
我不需要它们。
I'll have you know
我会让你知道
I got this black eye in a fight.
我在一场战斗中被打肿了。
A fight?
打架？
Well, there's no
shame in losing.
嗯，没有
因失败而感到耻辱。
Lose?
失去？
Sandy, I taught the fish
who tangled with me
桑迪，我教了鱼
谁与我纠缠
a lesson he shan't soon forget.
他不会很快忘记这一教训。
Why?
为什么？
Did he write it down?
他写下来了吗？
No, I engraved it
on his pain gland.
不，是我刻的
在他的疼痛腺上。
Well, what type of man scuffles
boots with you and loses?
那么，什么样的男人会扭打呢？
和你一起靴子然后输了？
Oh, this was no mere man.
哦，这不仅仅是一个男人。
He was the notorious outlaw
他是臭名昭著的歹徒
Jack M. Crazyfish!
杰克·M·疯狂鱼！
Jack M. Crazyfish?
杰克·M·疯狂鱼？
It all happened
late last night...
这一切都发生了
昨晚很晚...
...I was walking home
from work... alone
……我正走回家
下班...独自一人
when all of a sudden, crazyfish
sprang up out of nowhere.
突然之间，疯狂的鱼
凭空出现。
He threw a giant tire
他扔了一个巨大的轮胎
at the back of my head.
在我的脑后。
Then, he stood over me to gloat.
然后，他站在我身边幸灾乐祸。
I jumped up and karate
kicked his hairpiece
right off of its snaps.
我跳起来空手道
踢了他的假发
就在它的快照上。
He was so ashamed
he ran all the way home
他很羞愧
他一路跑回家
leaving behind a pool of tears.
留下一滩泪水。
Which I then proceeded to scoop
up in my victory tankard
然后我开始挖掘
在我的胜利酒杯中
and enjoy as a nice
refreshing beverage.
并享受作为一个美好的
提神饮料。
So how'd you get
the black eye then?
那你是怎么得到的
那么黑眼圈呢？
Oh, yeah, well, that's right.
哦，是的，嗯，没错。
I had miscalculated the
trajectory of my cup
我错误地计算了
我的杯子的轨迹
and the straw
jabbed me in the eye
和稻草
戳我的眼睛
giving me this awful shiner.
给我这个可怕的光泽。
Well, looks like you're late
for your day job, killer.
嗯，看来你来晚了
为了你的日常工作，杀手。
Aw, phooey.
噢，呸。
Late schmate.
迟到的施密特。
A tough guy like me can show up
to work whenever he wants.
像我这样的硬汉也能出现
他想什么时候工作就什么时候工作。
Adios.
再见。
SpongeBob is 13-1/2 minutes
late for duty.
海绵宝宝时长 13-1/2 分钟
上班迟到了。
I hope for his sake this means
he was in a horrible accident.
我希望为了他，这意味着
他遭遇了一场可怕的事故。
Well, looks like I was right
about the accident part.
嗯，看来我是对的
关于事故部分。
Oh.
哦。
Yeah, that's right, pal,
do the right thing.
是的，没错，朋友，
做正确的事。
Just keep on walking.
继续走吧。
Ugh, do you mind?
呃，你介意吗？
We're trying to have
a decent meal here.
我们正在努力拥有
在这里吃一顿像样的饭。
That's right.
这是正确的。
SpongeBob, I'm...
海绵宝宝，我...
Dah-dah-dah-dah,
I'm just gonna stop you
right there, Squidward.
哒哒哒哒哒，
我只是要阻止你
就在那里，章鱼哥。
Spare you the oxygen.
省点氧气吧
We all know you weaker folk
can't afford to waste it.
我们都知道你们这些弱者
不能浪费它。
All right folks, listen up.
好吧，各位，听着。
'Cause I'm only gonna
say this once.
因为我只会
说这一次。
SpongeBob: Tough guys don't
like to repeat themselves.
海绵宝宝：硬汉不会
喜欢重复自己。
I'm talking to you, grandma!
我在跟你说话呢，奶奶！
Now I suppose all of
you are wondering
现在我想所有的
你想知道
how I got this black eye.
我怎么得了这个黑眼圈。
Squidward: Not really.
章鱼哥：不完全是。
All right, who said that?
好吧，谁说的？
Was it you, grandma?
是你吗，奶奶？
It was me,
I said it.
是我，
我说过了。
Well, folks, I don't happen
to see it as a shiner
好吧，伙计们，我不会发生这样的事
将其视为闪亮者
so much as a shining trophy
of my glorious triumph
我光荣的胜利
over the forces of evil.
战胜邪恶势力。
Oh, I know what
you're thinking.
哦，我知道什么
你在想。
Who in the name of Neptune
would want to tangle
谁以海王星的名义
会想要纠结
with a guy like
SpongeBob SquarePants?
和一个像这样的人
海绵宝宝？
Well, I'll tell you who?
好吧，我告诉你是谁？
It was a peaceful morning
in Bikini Bottom.
这是一个宁静的早晨
在比基尼底部。
I emerged from
my fruit-shaped bungalow
fresh as a bee
我从
我的水果形平房
像蜜蜂一样新鲜
When a wanton cry of distress
当肆意的哀嚎时
pounded against my eardrum.
敲击着我的耳膜。
Hold it.
握住它。
Sponges don't have eardrums.
海绵没有耳膜。
He's right.
他是对的。
Hey, let's save all the
questions until the end.
嘿，让我们拯救所有
问题直到最后。
As I was saying...
正如我所说...
I quickly located
the source of the cry
我很快找到了
哭泣的源头
which was a victim
tied at my feet.
这是受害者
绑在我脚边。
Don't worry,
I'll save you.
别担心，
我会救你的。
...I assured...
...我保证...
when a large bowling pin
struck me in the face.
当一个大保龄球瓶时
打在我脸上。
The hurler was none other
than Jack M. Crazyfish.
投掷者不是别人
比杰克·M·疯狂鱼。
And I could tell by that
cold sore on his lip
我可以看出
他嘴唇上有唇疱疹
that today he meant business.
今天他是认真的。
With cat-like reflexes
拥有猫般的反应能力
I preempted his attack.
我先发制人了他的攻击。
But the scoundrel
had me sabotaged
但恶棍
让我破坏了
and I fell face down on
a pile of extra large staples.
我脸朝下倒在
一堆超大的订书钉。
He lunged at me.
他向我扑来。
But I got him in the ribs with
my novelty feather duster.
但我让他的肋骨
我的新奇鸡毛掸子。
Down he fell like a mighty oak.
他像一棵巨大的橡树一样倒下了。
And there he lay.
他就躺在那里。
The very thought
of being vanquished
正是这个想法
被征服的
made Jack M. Crazyfish
burst into tears.
杰克·M·疯狂鱼
泪流满面。
The force of his crying
was so strong
他哭泣的力量
太强了
I had to take evasive action.
我不得不采取回避行动。
But one of the blasts
went haywire
但其中一场爆炸
失控了
and hit me right in the face.
并打在我脸上。
And that's how I got
this black eye
这就是我得到的
这个黑眼圈
by giving Jack M. Crazyfish
通过给予 Jack M. Crazyfish
the whompin' of a lifetime.
一生难忘的人。
Whoo... Football!
哇...足球！
Uh, what did you say
he looked like again?
呃，你说什么
他又看起来像什么了？
Oh, kind of tall,
handlebar moustache...
哦，有点高，
车把小胡子...
Little Green hat?
小绿帽子？
I kind of thought it was teal
我还以为是青色
but that sounds like
him all right.
但这听起来像
他没事。
Wait a second.
等一下。
How did you know he was
wearing a green hat  ?
你怎么知道他是
戴着绿帽子？
He's... real.
他是……真实的。
I'm looking
for SpongeBob Square...
我在找
对于海绵宝宝广场...
Mr. Crazyfish, please
don't skin me alive.
疯狂鱼先生，请
别活剥我的皮。
I made all that stuff up.
这些都是我编出来的。
I was just kidding about
whomping you, right folks?
我只是开玩笑
打你，对吧伙计们？
You remember.
你记得。
I liked the part
where you told us
我喜欢这个部分
你告诉我们的地方
how he was crying like a baby.
他哭得像个婴儿。
... Hi, Gary.
……嗨，加里。
All right, look.
好吧，看吧。
I had a toothpaste tube,
like this.
我有一个牙膏管，
像这样。
But I couldn't get it open
'cause the cap was stuck.
但我无法打开它
因为盖子被卡住了。
And I guess...
我猜...
I haven't been working my
arms out that much lately.
我还没有工作过
最近手臂这么大。
So I opened it up-
like this.
于是我打开了它——
像这样。
Then I was walkin', like this.
然后我就这样走着。
And I didn't see where
the cap went, like this.
而且我没看到哪里
帽子就这样走了。
I slipped on it
我在上面滑倒了
and I landed right on my wrench,
like this.
我正好落在我的扳手上，
像这样。
And I gave myself a black eye,
like this.
我还给自己打了个黑眼圈
像这样。
Uh, like these.
呃，就像这些。
So you see?
所以你看到了吗？
I made it all up so I could
keep from looking stupid.
我编造了这一切，这样我就可以
不要显得愚蠢。
Makes sense, doesn't it?
有道理，不是吗？
Uh, not really.
呃，不是真的。
I'm here because I heard you
make a really good Krabby Patty.
我来这里是因为我听到了你的声音
做一个非常好的蟹肉饼。
One super hot and delicious
custom order Krabby Patty
with extra sauce, milord.
一份超级热又好吃
定制订单 蟹肉饼
加额外的酱汁，大人。
Served directly to your
waiting... Ow!
直接送达您的
等待着……哎哟！
Head and neck area.
头部和颈部区域。
Sir, please, I am so sorry.
先生，求求你了，我很抱歉。
Where I'm from,
sorry don't cut it.
我来自哪里，
抱歉，别剪了。
We settle things
in a different kind of way.
我们解决事情
以一种不同的方式。
SpongeBob: No!
海绵宝宝：不！
Man: Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy
男：人鱼男
和藤壶男孩
have been captured
by the evil Man Ray.
已被捕获
由邪恶的曼·雷所为。
...tickled to the point
of wetting themselves
……痒到了极点
弄湿自己
and sent on
a conveyor belt of doom
并发送到
厄运的传送带
to their watery grave.
到他们的水坟墓。
We cannot escape,
Barnacle Boy.
我们无法逃避，
藤壶男孩。
He's too strong.
他太强了。
Like the unbeatable taste
喜欢无与伦比的味道
of a Krusty Kids Meal.
Krusty 儿童餐。
The delicious new treat
no mortal can resist?
美味的新款待
没有凡人能够抗拒？
Yup.
是的。
Ooh, I just love the
little Pip-Squeak Patty
哦，我只是喜欢
小匹普-吱吱帕蒂
small fries
and cold juice product.
小薯条
和冷果汁产品。
Man: Of course you do,
Man Ray.
男：你当然知道，
曼·雷.
Everyone loves
the new Krusty Kids Meal.
每个人都喜欢
新推出的 Krusty 儿童餐。
And for a limited time,
get your free toy inside.
并且在有限的时间内，
把你的免费玩具放进去。
How can I be evil
with flavors this good?
我怎么可以邪恶
味道这么好？
Krabs calls that a commercial?
蟹老板称这是广告？
Who'd fall for that schlock?
谁会爱上那个混蛋？
Say...
说...
Something  is  going
on over there.
有事发生
就在那儿。
Ooh.
哦。
The Krusty Krab welcomes...
蟹堡王欢迎...
the Tarpon twins
海鲢双胞胎
Here are your
Krabby Kids Meals.
这是你的
蟹蟹儿童餐。
Never trust kids, Squidward.
永远不要相信孩子，章鱼哥。
Never trust kids.
永远不要相信孩子。
Gotta hand it to ya, boy.
必须把它交给你，孩子。
Gettin' Mermaid Man and Barnacle
Boy to shill for me restaurant
获取美人鱼人和藤壶
男孩托我去餐厅
was a stroke of genius.
真是天才之举。
All in the line
of duty, Mr. Krabs.
一切都在一线
蟹老板，我的职责。
Wasn't it great, Squidward?
不是很棒吗，章鱼哥？
Great?
伟大的？
Those little savages
tried to kill me.
那些小野人
试图杀了我。
Yeah, but it's  so  worth it
是的，但是非常值得
when you get to work in these.
当你开始从事这些工作时。
Stupid kid.
傻孩子。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
What's this?
这是什么？
Karen?
凯伦？
My own wife.
我自己的妻子。
Oh, how Krabs mocks me.
哦，蟹老板多么嘲笑我啊。
Hi, honey.
嗨，亲爱的。
What's that?
那是什么？
A souvenir from
your boyfriend, Krabs?
纪念品来自
你的男朋友，蟹蟹？
Oh, pipe down.
哦，管下来。
I just went to get you
this Happy Hero Box.
我只是去接你
这个快乐英雄盒子。
Well...
出色地...
Thanks, babe,
you're too good to me.
谢谢，宝贝，
你对我太好了。
A Mermaid Man action figure?
美人鱼人可动人偶？
And a Barnacle Boy eraser?
还有藤壶男孩橡皮擦？
Look at me,
I'm Barnacle Boy.
看着我，
我是藤壶男孩。
Look at me,
I'm Mermaid Man.
看着我，
我是美人鱼男
Krabs...
螃蟹...
Sure...
当然...
Why didn't I think
of this before?
为什么我没想到
以前有过这个吗？
If Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy
can build Krabs up
如果人鱼男和藤壶男孩
可以建造螃蟹
they can tear him down, too.
他们也可以把他打倒。
Plankton: Ding dong.
浮游生物：叮咚。
Hello, boys.
你好，孩子们。
Both: What, what-what?
两人：什么，什么——什么？
I'm down here, fellas!
我在这儿，伙计们！
Who are you?
你是谁？
Oh, Professor Plankton.
噢，浮游生物教授。
Door-to-door salesman.
上门推销员。
My card.
我的卡。
Professor Plankton's
personal products?
浮游生物教授的
个人产品？
Say, you two look like a couple
of ladies' men, am I right?
话说你们两个像情侣啊
女装男装，我说得对吗？
I knew it.
我就知道。
Just look at that heroic chin.
只要看看那英勇的下巴就知道了。
Those chiseled features.
那些轮廓分明的特征。
That bra.
那个胸罩。
But what's this?
但这是什么？
Dandruff?
头皮？
I've got dandruff?
我有头皮屑吗？
You sure do.
你一定会的。
See?
看？
Oh, my.
哦，我的。
Eww.
呃。
A couple of studs like you
几个像你一样的螺柱
can't go around like this.
不能这样到处走。
Lucky for you,
Dr. Plankton's come prepared
你很幸运，
浮游生物博士有备而来
with Plankton's
Dandruff Control Shampoo.
与浮游生物的
去屑洗发水。
A little of this stuff
有点这个东西
and the ladies'll be breakin'
down your door.
女士们会崩溃的
下你的门。
Sign us up, Professor.
给我们报名吧，教授。
wise decision,
gentlemen.
明智的决定，
先生们。
Hey, what do we have here?
嘿，我们这里有什么？
You fellas look a little peaked.
你们这些家伙看起来有点高了。
Hmm, this shouldn't be.
嗯，这不应该是这样。
I wonder.
我想知道。
Say, this isn't
Professor Plankton's
Dandruff Control Shampoo.
说吧，这不是
浮游生物教授的
去屑洗发水。
It's Professor Plankton's
Mind  Control Shampoo.
这是浮游生物教授的
精神控制洗发水。
With conditioner.
带护发素。
Time to prepare for your
next role, fellas
是时候为您的
下一个角色，伙计们
as my zombies.
作为我的僵尸。
Children:  :
We want Mermaid Man.
儿童: :
我们想要美人鱼男。
We want Barnacle Boy.
我们想要藤壶男孩。
Children: We want Mermaid Man.
孩子们：我们想要美人鱼人。
We want Barnacle Boy.
我们想要藤壶男孩。
We want Mermaid Man.
我们想要美人鱼男。
Mr. Krabs: Uh... Hey, kids.
蟹老板：呃……嘿，孩子们。
Uh, well, there's Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy,
in the ball room.
呃，好吧，还有美人鱼男
和藤壶男孩，
在舞厅里。
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Go get those AWOL do-gooders
you talked me into hiring
去找那些擅离职守的行善者吧
你说服我去招聘
and bring their patoots
back here on the double.
并带来他们的爱国者
回到这里双。
Aye, aye Mr. Krabs.
是的，是的，蟹老板。
Back, you, back.
回来，你，回来。
SpongeBob: Mermaid Man and
Barnacle Boy, please?
藤壶男孩，可以吗？
And I'm kind of in a hurry.
我有点着急。
Ahh!
啊！
Oh, my gosh.
哦，天哪。
You guys live in a dump.
你们住在垃圾场里。
But we don't have
time for that right now.
但我们没有
现在是时候了。
We gotta get you back
to the Krusty Krab
我们得让你回来
到蟹堡王
for your special appearance.
为了你的特殊外表。
I'll take you.
我带你去。
Wow, I haven't seen you do
the spine-blaster since...
哇，我还没见过你这么做
脊椎爆破机自...
Since episode 647...
从第647集开始...
When you blasted
that guy's spine.
当你炸开的时候
那个人的脊椎。
You still got it.
你还是明白了。
Perch Perkins here,
live at the Krusty Krab.
鲈鱼珀金斯在这里，
住在蟹堡王。
We're just moments away from
an important press conference
我们距离
一个重要的新闻发布会
with Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy.
与美人鱼人
和藤壶男孩。
I have with me here Eugene Krabs
我和尤金·克拉布斯在一起
owner of the restaurant.
餐厅的老板。
Any thoughts, Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板，有什么想法吗？
: Oh, OK.
: 噢，好的。
We'll come back to you later.
我们稍后再联系您。
SpongeBob: Whoa...
海绵宝宝：哇…
Ladies and gentlemen!
女士们，先生们！
I present
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy.
我提出
美人鱼人和藤壶男孩。
Oh, boy...
哦，男孩……
everyone in Bikini Bottom
showed up.
比基尼泳裤中的每个人
出现了。
This is gonna be  so  sweet.
这会很甜蜜。
Mermaid Man, what is your
opinion of the Krabby Patty?
人鱼男，你是什么
对蟹黄派的看法？
Ooh, this is too easy.
哦，这太容易了。
Now just tell everyone that...
现在就告诉大家...
I, Mermaid Man, think that
Krabby Patties are, uh...
我，美人鱼男，认为
蟹肉饼是，呃……
Uh, what?
呃，什么？
They're terrible.
他们太可怕了。
You hate Krabby Patties.
你讨厌蟹肉饼。
I'm late for "snappy pabbies?"
我迟到了？
Barnacle Boy...
藤壶男孩...
We're late for...
我们迟到了...
Oh, for crying out loud.
哦，因为大声哭泣。
Tell them you
hate Krabby Patties.
告诉他们你
讨厌蟹肉饼。
What?
什么？
SpongeBob:  :
Mermaid Man.
海绵宝宝：：
美人鱼男.
What?
什么？
I brought you something
to refresh your memory.
我给你带来了一些东西
来刷新你的记忆。
Mermaid Man: Ooh,
a Krabby Patty.
人鱼男：哦，
蟹肉饼。
Would you look at that.
你能看一下吗？
Barnacle Boy.
藤壶男孩。
It's a Krabby Patty.
这是蟹黄饼。
Why these things are...
为什么这些东西是...
evil...
邪恶的...
Susie, no!
苏西，不！
I hate these nasty things, puh.
我讨厌这些讨厌的东西，噗。
And furthermore...
而且此外...
Let it be known
that I, Mermaid Man
让大家知道
我，人鱼男
prefer the delicious food
available at the Chum Bucket...
更喜欢美味的食物
可在 Chum Bucket 购买...
Your new favorite restaurant.
您最喜欢的新餐厅。
The Chum Bucket?
密友桶？
Plankton must be behind this.
浮游生物一定是这件事的幕后黑手。
Yes.
是的。
Yes... It's working!
是的...它正在工作！
Hold it right there.
把它握在那里。
You forgot your
Krabby Patties.
你忘记了你的
蟹肉饼。
Oh.
哦。
Krabby Patties.
蟹肉饼。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Those infernal Krabby Patties.
那些地狱般的蟹肉饼。
Their grease-fried deliciousness
他们的油煎美味
could be enough to free
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy.
可能足以释放
美人鱼人和藤壶男孩。
Not so fast.
没那么快。
You're not dealing with
an ordinary fry cook.
你不是在处理
一个普通的炒菜厨师。
It's time for you to meet...
你们见面的时间到了...
fry boy.
油炸男孩。
Defender of... uh-oh!
捍卫者……呃哦！
Fry boy.
油炸男孩。
Defender of the Krabby Patty.
克拉比帕蒂的防守者。
Yah!
啊！
Yes!
是的！
You lose, Plankton.
你输了，浮游生物。
Now watch as the Krabby Patties'
wholesome flavors
work their magic.
现在观看蟹黄肉饼的表演
有益健康的味道
发挥他们的魔力。
I did it.
我做到了。
I did it!
我做到了！
Look at all these customers.
看看所有这些客户。
In your face, Krabs.
在你的脸上，蟹蟹。
Yes!
是的！
So, uh... Where's the food?
那么，呃...食物在哪里？
Food?
食物？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Never thought I'd get this far.
从来没想过我会走到这一步。
It doesn't make sense.
这没有道理。
They should have been cured
once the pureness of
the Krabby Patties
他们应该已经被治愈了
一旦纯洁
蟹肉饼
entered their... That's it!
进入他们的...就是这样！
Mermaid Man and
Barnacle Boy are elderly.
美人鱼男人和
藤壶男孩已经上了年纪了。
Their poor aged tummies
must be having a hard time
digesting the food.
他们可怜的老肚子
一定过得很艰难
消化食物。
I know just what to do.
我知道该怎么做。
I'm back to my old self again.
我又变回原来的自己了。
Thanks to you, SpongeBob.
谢谢你，海绵宝宝。
And the delicious power
of Krabby Patties.
还有美味的力量
蟹肉饼。
Say, I could use
a couple more of those
说，我可以用
还有几个
and an order of Krabby fries.
和一份蟹黄薯条。
And a decent latrine.
还有一个像样的厕所。
Well, then, you guys
know where to go.
那么，你们
知道该去哪里。
All: To the Krusty Krab, away.
全体：去蟹堡，走吧。
Hey, everyone.
嘿，大家。
I made Chummy Joes.
我做了巧克力乔。